(Raj:)How do you know that?
(Howard:)Well, he was Italian.
(Howard:)It's a reasonable assumption.
(Raj:)Dude, can you even
open your mouth
(Raj:)without spewing a
cultural stereotype?
Oh, I-I'm sorry,
Galileo drank Diet Sprite.
(Howard:)Look, you're my best friend,
she's my girlfriend;
(Howard:)you should bond.
(Raj:)You know,
like you and my mom did.
(Raj:)Your mom creeps
the hell out of me.
(Howard:)Yes, but she's stopped
calling you Slumdog Millionaire.
(Raj:)I do appreciate that.
(Bernadette:)Here we go.
(Howard:)I'd like to propose a toast.
(Howard:)To science and friendship.
(Bernadette:)Hold on. Wait.
(Bernadette:)No, it's okay, go ahead.
(Leonard:)What?
(Bernadette:)Oh, I was working with
penicillin-resistant gonorrhea
in the lab today
(Bernadette:)and I was just trying to
remember if I washed my hands.
(Leonard:)Thanks for the steak, Wyatt.
(Penny's dad (Wyatt):)My pleasure.
(Penny's dad (Wyatt):)It's nice to have dinner
with a boyfriend of Penny's